<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Yitong Zou</title>
    <link>https://zouyitong.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Yitong Zou</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://zouyitong.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://zouyitong.github.io/posts/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zouyitong.github.io/posts/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Yitong (Amanda) Zou.
I am currently a Master of Financial Engineering student at Cornell University. You can find my education here.
I also have several project experiences.
Things I do in spare time.
Thank you for taking the time to visit my website. If you have any questions or just want to say hello, feel free to contact me via email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>https://zouyitong.github.io/posts/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zouyitong.github.io/posts/education/</guid>
      <description>Cornell University
Master of Engineering in Financial Engineering (Expected 2023.12)
Selected Courses: Intro to Machine Learning, Stochastic Calculus, Big Data Techniques, Valuation Principles, Python for Finance
University of Michigan, Ann Arbor
Bachelor of Science in Mathematics (2022.04)
Bachelor of Science in Economics (2022.04)
Selected Courses: Linear Algebra, Advanced Calculus, Probability Theory, Mathematical Statistics, Abstract Algebra, Intermediate Econometrics
Back to About Me</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interests</title>
      <link>https://zouyitong.github.io/posts/interests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zouyitong.github.io/posts/interests/</guid>
      <description>Photography Travelling Piano Baking Back to About Me</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://zouyitong.github.io/posts/project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zouyitong.github.io/posts/project/</guid>
      <description>Spring 2023: ORIE 5370 Optimization Modeling in Finance
Project Name: Long-Short trading strategy in Machine Learning The objective of our project is to develop and implement a Long-Short trading strategy based on machine learning techniques and optimization methods. We will construct our portfolio based on ML selected ranking factors which have strong correlation with well-performed/bad-performed stocks to maximize expected returns and minimize risk. Our focus is on all the stocks in the Russell 3000 index, and we will consider a range of macro, fundamental, and risk factors as potential predictors of stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
